









Language

Bulgarian English Turkish

Programming skills

- HTML
 CSS
 PHP
 Tailwind
 Bootstrap
 JavaScript
 Next.js
 PHP
 Laravel
 Symfony
 MySQL
- jQueryVue.jsMongoDB
- React.jsGitAJAXJira

Ersin Hyusein

Summary

I have been programing for 5 years. I have knowledge of backend and front-end programming. My greatest strength is web programming.

Skill Highlights

- Teamwork
- Strong decision marker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Good communication and organizational skills

Experience

07/2023 - Until now

Varna • Web Developer • MyPOS

• Web development, testing and implementation

10/2022 - 07/2023 Until now

Varna • Junior Full Stack Developer • James IT Services

• Web development, testing and implementation

04/2022 - 10/2022

Varna • IT support & consultant • ENERGO-PRO

• Testing and reporting of company software products

05/2021 - 10/2021

Varna • Manager of hookahs company • Briela Ltd.

04/2019 - 09/2019

Golden Sands • Currency cashier • Edives Ltd.

2018

Golden Sands • Experience in the field of touriysm

Education

- Master degree: Mobile and web technologies 2023 2024
 Varna, University of Economics
- Bachelor degree: Business Information System 2018 2022



Varna, University of Economics

Secondary school education: Sports Coach – 2013 - 2018
 Varna, Sport School "Georgi Benkovski"

Certifications

- One of the recipients of the CRAICT Award at UE Varna (Laureate) (Fund to support talented students) 2023.
- <u>Certificate for first place in 2022, "Review of student activities"</u> at the Department of Informatics with development;
- SAFe, Scaled Agile methodology certification;
- Microsoft Azure fundamentals certification;
- Certificate from IT Master Class 9 UE Varna;
- Certificate from IT Master Class 10 UE Varna;
- <u>Published report in the collection "Student Scientific</u> Conference";
- Certificate of computer literacy;
- Many sports achievements, medals, diplomas and cups.

Projects

Professional projects

- Website + account primarily for managing business processes. <u>Link</u>
 (MyPOS) (PHP, Symfony, React.js, Mobx, Bootstrap)
- Web platform for buying/selling automobiles (James IT Services)
 (PHP, Laravel, Vue.js, Tailwind)
- Web system for offering properties from banks. (in process)
 Link, Photos (James IT Services) (PHP, Laravel, Vue.js, Tailwind)

Personal projects

- Web system for appointments; Link 🕡
- Web-based system for managing workflow processes; Link ()
- Web-based system for searching and offering job positions;
 Link \(\mathbb{O} \)
- Web workflow system; Link O Photos, Video
- Web platform for comparing of prices and products from various websites, Master's thesis; <u>Link</u>
- Company system for process management; Link \(\overline{\chi}\)
- Pizza company system for process management. Link

Recommendations from employers

- James IT Services - Manager



